

English Language Teacher having more than four years of teaching experience (more than one year online) who is organized and effective at using efficient teaching methods while focusing on the individual needs of each participant. Extensive knowledge of differentiated methods of teaching. Moreover, proficient in the use of technology and computer applications.

Anisimova Yuliia

Phone:

+38 (098) 426 66 21

E-Mail:

anisimova.yuliia01@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/yuliia-anisimova-74a9a3235/

SKILL HIGHLIGHTS

- Critical thinking and problem solving
- Ability to work in team
- Communication skills
- Leadership
- Cultural Competence
- Creativity
- Computer Skills
- Organization
- Flexibility
- Accuracy
- Ability to learn quickly
- Ability to handle stress

LANGUAGES

English – C1 Ukrainian – Native speaker Russian – Native speaker

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Dec. 2020 – Jul. 2022

English Language Teacher (online) – Cloud Education Center, Poltava (Employment contract)

- Planning course material and activities.
- Teaching groups (2-5 students)/individual students (young learners, teens, adults) (online).
- Planning material and conducting a speaking club.
- Assessing the students' progress (e.g. homework, tests, etc.).
- Identify students with special requirements and create individualized plans.
- Managing classroom crises and resolving conflicts.
- Building trusting relationships with students, parents, teaching staff, and administrators.
- Remaining up-to-date with new learning software and new language teaching methods.

Mar. 2021 – Jun. 2021

English Language Teacher (online) – English Fun Centre, Poltava (Employment contract)

- Teaching groups (4-8 students).
- Preparing and conducting a training course for Ukrainian External Independent Evaluation (ZNO).

EDUCATION

Sep. 2016 – Dec. 2021

Master's Degree, Poltava National Pedagogical University

- Specialization 014.02 English Language and Literature
 Professional Qualification Master in Secondary Education (English Language and Literature). Teacher of the English Language and Literature
- Teaching English to 5-8-year-olds at SOVa Teacher's Training School (May 2020 – Jun 2020)
- International online conference "Modern Teaching Methods" (WinWin Teacher's Training Centre)